2008-07-20 After Guru Puja, Cabella, Italy
2008-07-20 Guru Puja sonrası, Cabella, Italya
You must form a central committee.
Bir merkezi komite oluşturmak zorundasınız.
[ UNCLEAR] ...one central committee.
[ANLAŞILMIYOR] ... Bir merkezi komite.
Maybe in London or maybe here.
Belki Londra’da veya belki de burada.
Wherever you feel  right. One Central Committee.
Nerede olmasının doğru olduğunu hissedersiniz. Bir merkezi komite.
And then you can inform them
Ve sonra onları bilgilendirebilirsiniz,
what is happening,   anything.
Ne olduğunu,   her şeyi.
Sahaji :  Yes Shri Mataji. Yes Shri Mataji.
Sahaji :  Evet Shri Mataji. Evet Shri Mataji.
Like the world council. We have a council Shri Mataji.
Like the world council. Bizim bir konseyimiz var, Shri Mataji.
Like the council. We have the council.
Konsey gibi. Bir konseyimiz var.
You have to tell what is happening.
Onlara ne olduğunu anlatmalısınız.
Some Central Committee you should have ..about say, five people.
Bir merkezi komitenizin olması gerek.. deyin ki, beş kişi.
Sahaji : Yes , communication, for communication.
Sahaji : Evet , iletişim, iletişim için.
No, No. For Communication.
Hayır, hayır. İletişim için.
Sahaji : Yes Shri Mataji.
Sahaji : Evet Shri Mataji.
Or in case any problem or anything.
Ya da herhangi bir sorun ya da başka bir şey olması durumunda.
So you can attend. Isn’t it?
Yani siz katılabilirsiniz, değil mi?
Sahaji : Yes Shri Mataji.
Sahaji : Evet Shri Mataji.
What?
Ne?
They are saying we will form it here. Here. Here.
Onu burada oluşturacağımızı söylüyorlar. Burada. Burada.
In Cabela. Will form in Cabella. In Cabella.
Cabella’da. Cabella’da oluşturacağız. Cabella’da.
Sahaji :  We will form a council. Committee , Committee.
Sahaji :  Bir konsey oluşturacağız. Komite , Komite.
Shri Mataji :  No , form it anywhere. Sahaji : Yes . Very well.
Shri Mataji :  Hayır, onu herhangi bir yerde oluşturun. Sahaji : Evet . Çok güzel.
Wherever you like.
Nerede isterseniz.
Take from 4-5 countries.
4-5 ülkeden alın.
Make one here, make ONE IN India.
Burada bir tane yapın, Hindistan’da da bir tane yapın.
Jai Shri Mataji
Jai Shri Mataji
- Isn’t it? Sahaji :  Yes, yes Shri Mataji.
- Değil mi? Sahaji :  Evet, evet Shri Mataji.
If there is any problem here,
Eğer burada herhangi bir problem varsa,
then you inform in India.
O zaman Hindistan’ı bilgilendirin.
Sahaji :  Jai  Shri Mataji.
Sahaji :  Jai  Shri Mataji.
In every detail.
Her bir detayda.
Sahaji : Yes Shri Mataji.Absolutely right. Absolutely right.
Sahaji : Evet Shri Mataji. Kesinlikle doğru. Kesinlikle doğru.
Put some Kajal in your eyes
Gözlerine biraz Kajal sür
Will look well.
İyi görünecektir.
You need to wear. You read a lot or what?
Bunu sürmen gerek. Çok mu yemek yiyorsun nedir?
Sahaji : Read? Not so much. Not so much.
Sahaji : Yemek mi? Çok fazla değil. Çok fazla değil.
Shri Mataji – What? Sahaji – Not so much.
Shri Mataji – Ne? Sahaji – Çok fazla değil.
Your eyes are getting little spoilt.
Gözlerin biraz bozuluyor.
Shri Mataji – Lets go. Sahaji : Jai Shri Mataji
Shri Mataji – Hadi gidelim. Sahaji : Jai Shri Mataji
Shri Mataji – Get the chair. Sahaji : Jai Shri Mataji.
Shri Mataji – Koltuğu getirin. Sahaji : Jai Shri Mataji.